http://www.usplastic.com/content/privacy.aspx?clickid=footer

Privacy Policy
We care about both your privacy and ours.
Information Practices
United States Plastic Corporation ("USP" or "we") understands that security and privacy are important issues for visitors to our www.usplastic.com web site (the "Site") and recognizes our obligation to keep your information secure and confidential. That is why we maintain the following standards to help protect information that personally identifies you. We may modify this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") at any time, and, accordingly, we urge you to frequently review the Policy. We will always apply the Policy under which your information was collected, unless we obtain your prior consent.
Collection of Information
You may be asked to voluntarily provide your name, billing address, shipping address, phone number, credit card number, email address or other personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") to make purchases or to have access to some features of the Site. By using the Site and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to our use of such information as described in this Policy. You may always refuse to provide your Personal Information, and this may lead to our inability to provide you with certain products or services. We or our business partners may also collect information that is anonymous, such as your IP address (a number used to identify your computer on the Internet) or the type of browser you are using ("Anonymous Information"), through the use of cookies or by other means.
Use of Information
USP may use your Personal Information for the following purposes: to process your orders and administer your account; to administer and improve the Site and related services; to create and maintain user profiles based on browsing or purchasing histories; to notify you of our products, services, promotional events or special offers that may be of interest to you; to provide Internet security; to allow third parties to provide you with information about their products, services, promotional events or special offers that may be of interest to you; or to meet any legal requirements. USP may supplement information collected on the Site with data from other sources, but this information will not be available online. If USP is involved in the sale of a substantial portion of its business assets, Anonymous or Personal Information may be among the transferred assets.
USP may work with our business partners who may perform certain functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, sending email messages, managing data, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. These business partners have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these specific functions and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally required to do so.
USP may use Anonymous Information to update the Site to make it more useful to you and other users. We reserve the right to maintain, update, disclose or otherwise use Anonymous Information, without limitation.
Privacy of Children
USP encourages parents and guardians to be aware of and participate in their children's online activities. We strictly adhere to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and will not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Information from any child under the age of 13 in any manner that violates this law.
Cookies
When you visit the Site, USP or a third-party advertiser may store or recognize some information on your computer in the form of a "cookie" or similar file that can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to tailor the Site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers or other software, you can erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored.Please refer to your browser instructions to learn more about these functions.If you reject cookies, functionality of the Site may be limited, and you may not be able to take advantage of many of the Site's features. The Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) allows for the central opting out of all of its members' cookies from a single opt-out page. To find out more, and opt out of NAI member cookies, click here.
Links
The Site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. USP is not responsible for the collection or use of your Personal or Anonymous Information at any third party sites.
Security
We have policies and procedures in place to protect the privacy and confidentiality of your Personal Information that we collect and maintain. All Personal Information is stored on our secured servers, behind a firewall at a data center with access to data strictly controlled. USP uses security measures, including: Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) encryption technology for portions of the Site, Netscreen firewall for server hardware security and AS/400 security standards for legacy data. Neither USP nor its affiliates guarantees electronic transactions made through the Site.
Please do not share any online user name or password with anyone, and please update your password at regular intervals. These steps will help to ensure the security of your Personal Information. Any unauthorized use of the Site may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution.
Access of Information
You may access and update your own Personal Information on your account management page. We appreciate your maintaining currently accurate information on the Site.
Contacting USP and Resolving Problems
If you have any questions or comments about this Policy or wish to be removed from the USP database, please contact us by email at usp@usplastic.com or by phone at 800-809-4217. Please provide a concise communication with complete information, including your contact information. We are committed to fairly resolving all disputes and to only using your Personal Information as described in this policy.
If you are a resident of California, please click here for California-specific disclosures.
This item does not come with a cap.
[Item Description]
